<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Automation Steeg and Hoffmeyer GmbH</title><link>https://automation-gmbh.github.io/homepage/en/</link><description>Recent content on Automation Steeg and Hoffmeyer GmbH</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>de-DE</language><atom:link href="https://automation-gmbh.github.io/homepage/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Company</title><link>https://automation-gmbh.github.io/homepage/en/company/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://automation-gmbh.github.io/homepage/en/company/</guid><description>The company The Automation und Steeg Hoffmeyer GmbH was founded in 1972 with the aim to automate industrial value chains. Core task was to find efficient technology solutions. The company offered consulting, construction and design of special machines and additional equipment. For 40 years the Automation Steeg und Hoffmeyer GmbH has been a reliable and competent partner for the production of semi- and fully automated machinery for glass and pharmaceutical industry.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://automation-gmbh.github.io/homepage/en/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://automation-gmbh.github.io/homepage/en/contact/</guid><description>Contact Contact us
Automation Steeg und Hoffmeyer GmbH Mainzer Landstraße 155 55257 Budenheim Germany
Phone: +49 6139 29270 Fax: +49 6139 292729
E-Mail: info (at) automation-gmbh (dot) com Web: www.automation-gmbh (dot) com</description></item><item><title>Data Protection</title><link>https://automation-gmbh.github.io/homepage/en/dataprotection/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://automation-gmbh.github.io/homepage/en/dataprotection/</guid><description>DATA PROTECTION:
Automation Steeg und Hoffmeyer GmbH
Mainzer Landstraße 155
55257 Budenheim
Telefon 0613929270
&amp;ldquo;This privacy policy clarifies the type, scope, and purpose of the collection and use of visitor/user data by the provider as the data protection officer. If you have any questions regarding data protection, you can reach us during regular business hours.
We appreciate your interest in our website. The protection of your personal data during the collection, processing, and use when visiting our website is an important concern to us.</description></item><item><title>Imprint</title><link>https://automation-gmbh.github.io/homepage/en/imprint/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://automation-gmbh.github.io/homepage/en/imprint/</guid><description>Automation Steeg und Hoffmeyer GmbH
Mainzer Landstraße 155
55257 Budenheim
Telefon 0613929270
Telefax
Steuernummer
Disclaimer:
Despite careful content control, we assume no liability for the content of external links. The operators of the linked pages are solely responsible for their content.
Note on dispute resolution in consumer matters:
Platform of the EU Commission for online dispute resolution: http://ec.europa.eu/consumers/odr We are neither obliged nor willing to participate in a dispute settlement procedure before a consumer arbitration board.</description></item></channel></rss>